aidanbooth.com 2019-06-01

# Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Our Privacy Policy (dated 23.4.2018)

We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected.

This is our privacy policy (dated 23.4.2018). Our services and information provided, and therefore this policy are aimed at people aged over the age of 18.

**The information you need to know about us:**

We are Blueprint Information Products and/or Volta Marketing Limited (herein referred to as ‘the company’), doing business as AidanBooth.com.

**The information we collect and how we use it**

When subscribing to an email list with us, completing a survey, downloading software tools or information, or buying one of our products, you may be asked to share information about who you are and your contact information. This will include but not be limited to your name, email, and phone number. Where billing information is required we will need an address.

You should understand that any information that you provide via this web site may be used by us to contact you regarding delivery of information, important notifications, promotional material, or any matter relating to AidanBooth.com and related services, your request or use of this web site.

This site incorporates the use of Cookies. Cookies are small data text files that are sent from a server computer during a browsing session. Cookies are typically stored on your computers hard drive and are used by Websites to simulate a continuous connection to that site. In order to make our site more responsive to your needs we use cookies to track and manage information relative to your specific interests. In this way we can tailor our site to your needs, deliver a better and more personalised service and track the pages on our site that you visit. The use of cookies automatically identifies your browser to our computers whenever you interact with our site. Your browser options allow you to disable cookies. You should note that if you do disable cookies, you may not be able to access all the services on this site.

**Who we share your data with**

The data processors we use for our business operations who process your data under our control include:

– Aweber.com for email marketing campaigns  
– FloatHosting.com who provide website hosting  
– Rackspace.com who provide website hosting  
– Google.com (analytics) who provide website tracking and statistical services  
– Facebook.com who track website visitor  
– GoToWebinar who provide our webinar hosting platform  
– Clicky.com who provide website tracking  
– VWO.com who provide website split testing solutions

**Sharing your data with other 3rd partie** s

Should you register on this website to download any 3rd party content, we may pass your contact information to 3rd parties who either a) are partners of the event in question or b) are providers of the content you have downloaded. In the process of registering for an event or accessing content, you will be reminded of the fact that your data will be shared with named 3rd parties. We may also share your details under special circumstances such as when we believe in good faith that it is required by law.

**How long we keep your personal information**

We will keep your personal information until a period of 36 months has passed since you have engaged, clicked on, opened, or replied to one of our email communications.

In certain circumstances, we have a statutory obligation to keep your personal information for a set period of time for example financial information (normally 6-7 years) for financial auditing purposes.

**How to keep your personal information up-to-date**

It’s important for both you and us that your personal information is correct. If you believe this not to be the case and you are registered on this website then please contact us and ask that we update your details. You can do this by submitting a support ticket at http://support.blueprintcentral.com.

**How you can find out about the information we hold about you**

You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you.

If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please email us using the contact details in this policy.

We will get in contact to verify your identity and if we do hold information about you we will:

– give you a description of it  
– tell you why we are holding it  
– let you have a concise and clear copy of the information

**Our legal basis for processing your personal information**

When we are communicating with you regarding products and services you may be interested in receiving from us or our partners in the future our basis for processing is our legitimate interest (as we are communicating with you in the context of your corporate activity and identity and not in relation to your private life we believe this to be reasonable and fair behaviour in the context of our audience. Of course you will always have the opportunity to object as detailed below).

**Asking us to suppress or remove your personal information**

Should you wish to not receive information from us in future then you can quickly action this by clicking the unsubscribe link you will find on our marketing e-mails or by sending your details to support@blueprintcentral.com and we will quickly suppress your data.

Should you further wish for us to remove your information entirely (and assuming we have no other obligation to keep it) then please let us know and we will do this – but we would encourage you to let us use it for suppression purposes only.

**What to do if you have a complaint**

If you have a complaint please contact us using the contact information provided in this privacy policy so that we can address your request promptly.

**Links to other websites**

We link our website directly to other sites. This privacy notice does not cover the links within our site linking to other websites and organisations. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on the other websites you visit.

**Your use of our services**

Please be sure you are aware of these policy terms while you use our site. Should our terms change these will be shown on this page, and we may place notices on other pages of the web site, so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times.

**Copyright © 2003-2018  
Aidan Booth t/a AidanBooth.com and/or Blueprint Information Products**
